[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these describes best the location of the volcanic island of Krakatau (sometimes erroneously called Krakatoa), which had a well-known and devastating eruption on August 23, 1883?", "correct_answer": "Between Java and Sumatra", "incorrect_answers": ["West of New Guinea", "East of Java", "Off the coast of Borneo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the western movie For a Few Dollars More, how does Colonel Douglas Mortimer (Lee Van Cleef) get involved with Indios gang?", "correct_answer": "He opens a stolen safe for them.", "incorrect_answers": ["He guns down Clint Eastwoods character.", "He helps them rob the bank in El Dorado.", "He helps them rob the bank in El Paso."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the movie The Great Escape released?", "correct_answer": "1963", "incorrect_answers": ["1965", "1964", "1962"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Phantom of the Opera, Christines dad called her by what name?", "correct_answer": "Little Lotte", "incorrect_answers": ["Angel of Music", "Little Christine", "Laura Little"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In humans, which of these organs belongs to the integumentary system?", "correct_answer": "Skin", "incorrect_answers": ["Tonsils", "Liver", "Pharynx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which military conflict does the 1987 film Full Metal Jacket concern?", "correct_answer": "Vietnam War", "incorrect_answers": ["Korean War", "World War II", "World War I"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first Disney production to show the death of a main character?", "correct_answer": "Lion King", "incorrect_answers": ["Bambi", "Pocahontas", "Peter Pan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term refers to the distance between repeating units of a wave pattern and is commonly designated by the Greek letter lambda (\u03bb).", "correct_answer": "Wavelength", "incorrect_answers": ["Amp", "Wave distance", "Volt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This programming language that allowed non-scientists to use computers was developed in 1963 by John Kemeny and Thomas Kurtz.", "correct_answer": "BASIC", "incorrect_answers": ["PASCAL", "COBOL", "Visual BASIC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Irish it is Taim ingra leat. In Hebrew it is Ani ohev otah. In Hungarian it is Sz eretiek. In Dutch it is ik houd van jou. What is it in English?", "correct_answer": "I love you.", "incorrect_answers": ["How are you today?", "Good morning", "Sleep well."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most bear species are omnivores and their diet consists mainly of what?", "correct_answer": "Mast", "incorrect_answers": ["Tubers", "Leaves", "Grass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What two original Back to the Future characters were not portrayed by their original actors in the sequels?", "correct_answer": "Jennifer and George", "incorrect_answers": ["George and Lorraine", "Marty and Doc", "Jennifer and Lorraine"]}]